Inventory of O.41 - Collection of Lists and Documentation Regarding Those Who Perished and Those Who Were Persecuted During the Holocaust Period O.41
O.41 - Collection of Lists and Documentation Regarding Those Who Perished and Those Who Were Persecuted During the Holocaust Period
- List of Jews from Nadvornaya who were murdered, 05/1942, date empty; The file was created by רב קולסניק; 1 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1127
  Nadvornaya,Nadworna,Stanislawow,Poland
  List of Jews from Nadvornaya who were murdered, 05/1942
- List of Jews from the Sniatyn district who were murdered in the Szeparowce forest, 1942-1943, Список евреев, жителей города Снятын и различных деревень Снятинского района Ивано-Франковской области, расстрелянных ГЕСТАПО во время немецко-фашистской оккупации.; date empty; The file was created by רב קולסניק; 7 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1134
  Kulachkivtsi,Kolomyja,Stanislawow,Poland; Mikulintsy,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Budilov,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Shevchenkovo,Dolina,Stanislawow,Poland; Borshchiv,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Prutovka,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Beleluya,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Gankovtsy,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Snyatin,Sniatyn,Stanislawow,Poland; Szeparowce Area,forest,Murder Site,Poland; Balintsy,Kolomyja,Stanislawow,Poland
  List of Jews from the Sniatyn district who were murdered in the Szeparowce forest, 1942-1943
- List of Jews from Dolina who were murdered in the Dolina Ghetto, 1942, Список евреев, жителей города Долина Ивано-Франковской области, расстрелянных ГЕСТАПО во время немецко-фашистской оккупации.; date empty; The file was created by רב קולסניק; 3 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1139
- List of Jews from the Ottynia district who were murdered in the Szeparowce forest, 1942, Список евреев, жителей Отынийского района Ивано-Франковской области, расстрелянных ГЕСТАПО во время немецко-фашистской оккупации.; date empty; The file was created by רב קולסניק; 2 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1143
  Ottynia Area,Tlumacz,Stanislawow,Poland; Szeparowce Area,forest,Murder Site,Poland
  List of Jews from the Ottynia district who were murdered in the Szeparowce forest, 1942
- List of Jews from the Pochinok district who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; The file was created by Russian Research and Educational "Holocaust" Center; 2 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1158
  Pochinok,Pochinok,Smolensk,Russia (USSR); <>,Pochinok,Smolensk,Russia (USSR)
  List of Jews from the Pochinok district who perished during the Holocaust
- List of Jews from the Gers district who perished during the Holocaust and a list of non-Jews from the area who perished during World War II, date empty; 10 List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/1147
  <>,Gers,<>,France
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Mme Zeglany Pierrete
  List of Jews from the Gers district who perished during the Holocaust and a list of non-Jews from the area who perished during World War II
- List of de Beer family members from the Netherlands who perished in Auschwitz and Sobibor camps, Lijst van omgekomen familieleden; date empty; 3 List of murdered Jews xerox; O.41/1331
  <>,<>,<>,The Netherlands; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Sobibor,Extermination Camp,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Manuel P. de Groot
  List of de Beer family members from the Netherlands who perished in Auschwitz and Sobibor camps
- List of Jews from Stodolishche, Krasnoye Znamya and Pochinok who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; The file was created by Russian Research and Educational "Holocaust" Center; 1 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1155
  Stodolishche,Stodolishche,Smolensk,Russia (USSR); Pochinok,Pochinok,Smolensk,Russia (USSR); Krasnoye Znamya,Stodolishche,Smolensk,Russia (USSR)
  List of Jews from Stodolishche, Krasnoye Znamya and Pochinok who perished during the Holocaust
- List of Jews from Vinnitsa who perished during the Holocaust, from the Memorial Book, "Kniga Skorboti Urkaiyny", date empty; 9 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1112
  List of Jews from Vinnitsa who perished during the Holocaust, from the Memorial Book, "Kniga Skorboti Urkaiyny"
- List of Jews from the Cherven district who died as Red Army soldiers, date empty; 4 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers File; O.41/1218
  Jewish soldiers in the Red Army; <>,Cherven,Minsk,Belorussia (USSR)
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אינה גרסימובה
  List of Jews from the Cherven district who died as Red Army soldiers
  The list/s contain approximately 63 names
- List of Jews from Kodyma and the Kodyma vicinity who were murdered during the Holocaust, based on the book "Zhiviye i mertvye" by Petr Yefimov, Список имен жертв Холокоста, приведеных на стр.83-108 книги " Живые и Мертвые" автора Петра Ефимова, издание 2008 года; 2008-2008; The file was created by פטר יפימוב; 14 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1165
  Mass murders; Kodyma,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Shershentsy,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Krutyye,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Grabovo,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); <>,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Borshchi,Kotovsk,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Kodyma,Murder Site; Pisarevka,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Labushnoye,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Kodima,Kodyma,Moldaviya ASSR,Ukraine (USSR); Britovka,Cetatea Alba,Bessarabia,Romania
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אליעזר בלושטיין
  List of Jews from Kodyma and the Kodyma vicinity who were murdered during the Holocaust, based on the book "Zhiviye i mertvye" by Petr Yefimov
  The list/s contain approximately 510 names
- Section from a list of Jews from Kirovograd who perished during the Holocaust, including relatives of Raisa (Ninburg) Gertonskaya, date empty; The file was created by מרכז קהילתי יהודי "חסד שלמה"; 4 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons Original and Xerox Handwritten, original; O.41/1169
  Mass murders; Kirovograd,Kirovograd City,Kirovograd,Ukraine (USSR)
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Raisa Gertopskaya
  Section from a list of Jews from Kirovograd who perished during the Holocaust, including relatives of Raisa (Ninburg) Gertonskaya
- List of Jews from Hotin who were murdered, 09/07/1941, and a section of the testimony of Rachel Katz, a survivor of the mass murder, date empty; The file was created by ציליה פינוס; 5 List of murdered Jews Testimony Copy, handwritten Handwritten, original xerox; O.41/1185
  Mass murders; Memorials; Murder of Jews by Romanians; Hotin,Hotin,Bessarabia,Romania
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by פיוטר פינוס
  List of Jews from Hotin who were murdered, 09/07/1941, and a section of the testimony of Rachel Katz, a survivor of the mass murder
  - List of Jews from Hotin who were murdered, 09/07/1941; the names appear on a memorial stone established in Hotin, date empty; 1 List of murdered Jews; O.41/1185.1
    Mass murders; Hotin,Hotin,Bessarabia,Romania
    List of Jews from Hotin who were murdered, 09/07/1941; the names appear on a memorial stone established in Hotin
- List of Jews from the Gorki district, Belorussia, who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; The file was created by וולדימיר לפשיץ; 13 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish partisans File; O.41/1200
  Partisans - Jews; Anti-Nazi underground; <>,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Shooting of the Gorki area Jews at the Bely Ruchey point (urochische), October 1941
  List of Jews from the Gorki district, Belorussia, who perished during the Holocaust
  - List of Jews from the Gorki district who perished during the Holocaust, Партизаны, подпольщики, мирные жители Горецкого района, погибшие в годы Великой Отечественной войны; date empty; 3 List of murdered Jews; O.41/1200.1
    Anti-Nazi underground; Partisans - Jews; Gorki,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Gory,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Lenino,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Rudkovshchina,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); <>,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Medvedovka,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Volyntsevo,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR)
    List of Jews from the Gorki district who perished during the Holocaust
  - List of Jews from Gorki who were murdered in Beliy Ruchey, 07/10/1941, Мирные жители, расстрелянные 7 октября 1941 г., похороненные в братской могиле в урочище Белый Ручей, г.Горки.; date empty; 10 List of murdered Jews; O.41/1200.2
    Gorki,Beliy Ruchey,plot,Murder Site,Belorussia (USSR); Gorki,Gorki,Mogilev,Belorussia (USSR); Shooting of the Gorki area Jews at the Bely Ruchey point (urochische), October 1941
    List of Jews from Gorki who were murdered in Beliy Ruchey, 07/10/1941
    The list/s contain approximately 349 names
- List of fighters in the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising who perished during the Uprising, Lista poległych obrońcow ghetta Warszawskiego; 1962-1962; The file was created by Kultura, 3/173 1962; 2 List of murdered Jews List of murdered persons File; O.41/1161
  Warszawa,Ghetto; Warsaw Ghetto Uprising
  List of fighters in the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising who perished during the Uprising The list was taken from a book; Kultura, 3/173, 1962, pp. 92-93.
- Lists of Jews from the Chernigov region who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers; lists prepared, 2008, Программа Память. Материалы исследования мест массового расстрела евреев во время оккупации фашистскими войсками Черниговской области (25 августа 1941 - 30 сентября 1943 года); 07/2008-09/2008; The file was created by Jewish Confederation of Ukraine; 318 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph File; O.41/1180
  Jewish soldiers in the Red Army; Mass murders; Ukrainian collaborators; Murder of Jews by Ukrainians; <>,<>,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kiev,Kiev City,Kiev,Ukraine (USSR); Chernigov,Chernigov City,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Shooting of the Chernigov Jews, September 1941; Murder of Jewish women, elderly people and children from Shchors in Chernigov, January 1942; Shooting of the Chernigov Jews, winter 1941-1942
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Ilya Levitas
  Lists of Jews from the Chernigov region who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers; lists prepared, 2008 Sources: - Regional archives of Chernigov; - Branch of the regional archives in Nezhin; - Memorial book of the Chernigov region, Ukraine, Volumes 1-10, Kiev, 1993-1997; - Book, "Skorbota Ukrainy", Chernigov region, Volumes 1-10, Chernigov, 2003-2007; - Book, "The Chernigov region during World War II (1941-1945)", Kiev, 1978; - Book, "1,300 years of History in Chernigov" including a collection of documents and materials, Kiev, 1990.
  - Lists of Jews from the Ichnya district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Ичнянский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 1 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.1
    <>,Ichnya,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Ichnya,Ichnya,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Parafiyevka,Ichnya,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Bakhmach (Town),Bakhmach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Vereskuny,Ivanitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Ichnya district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Kulikovka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Куликовский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 2 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.2
    <>,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kladkovka,Komarovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nezhin,town,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Chernigov,city,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Gorbovo,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Veresoch,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kovchin,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kulikovka,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Buda,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Baklanova Muraveyka,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Vershinova Muraveyka,Kulikovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Kulikovka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Nosovka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Носовский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 2 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.3
    <>,Nosovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nosovka,Nosovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Selishche,Nosovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nezhin,town,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Makeyevka,Losinovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Nosovka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Bakhmach district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Бахмачский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 6 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph; O.41/1180.4
    <>,Bakhmach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Bakhmach (Town),Bakhmach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Dmitrovka,Dmitriyevka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Grigorovka,Dmitriyevka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Peski,Bakhmach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Baturin,Baturin,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Pliski,Bakhmach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Bakhmach district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Borzna district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Борзнянский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 8 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.5
    <>,Borzna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Borzna,Borzna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Shapovalovka Area,vicinity,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Pliski,Bakhmach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kerbutovka,Baturin,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Gorodishche,Baturin,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Novyye Mlyny,Baturin,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Berestovets,Komarovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nezhin,town,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Nikolayevka,<>,<>,Ukraine (USSR); Golovenki,Baturin,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Obmachev,Baturin,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Shapovalovka,Borzna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Borzna district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 91 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Kozelets district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Козелецкий район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 22 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.6
    <>,Kozelets,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kozelets,Kozelets,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Oster,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Oster,airport,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Birki,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Krasilovka,Olishevka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Chernigov,city,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Maksim,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Chemer,Olishevka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Krekhayev,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Karpilovka,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Yevminka,Kozelets,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Yemeliyanov,Kozelets,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Sorokoshichi,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Okuninov,Oster,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Podlesnoye,Olishevka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Kozelets district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 480 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Mena district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Менский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 25 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.7
    <>,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Mena,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Makoshino,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Berezna,Berezna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Chernigov,city,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Dyagova,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Voloskovtsy,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Domnitsa,Berezna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Feskovka,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Stolnoye,Berezna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Begach,Berezna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Danilovka,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Blistova,Mena,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Semenovka,Berezna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Leninovka,Berezna,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Mena district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 410 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Sosnitsa district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Сосницкий район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 16 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.8
    <>,Sosnitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Sosnitsa,Sosnitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Vyunishche,Sosnitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Masalayevka,Sosnitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Lavy,Sosnitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Avdeyevka,Ponornitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Dolinskoye,Sosnitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Sosnitsa district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 307 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Srebnoye district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Сребнянсий район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 1 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.9
    <>,Srebnoye,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kharitonovka,Srebnoye,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Priluki,Плискуновка,suburb,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Karpilovka,Srebnoye,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Podol,Srebnoye,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Vaskovtsy,Srebnoye,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Srebnoye district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Shchors district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Щорский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 17 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.10
    <>,Shchors,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Shchors,Shchors,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Shchors Area,forest,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Chernigov,Chernigov City,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nosovka,Nosovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Snovsk,Shchors,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Shchors district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Priluki district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Прилукский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 42 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph; O.41/1180.11
    <>,Priluki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Priluki,Priluki City,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Priluki,Плискуновка,suburb,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Linovitsa,Priluki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Ladan,Priluki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Malaya Devitsa,Malaya Devitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Rudovka,Priluki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Polova,Priluki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Tolkachovka,Malaya Devitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Chernyakhovka,<>,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Priluki district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 1059 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Bobrovitsa district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Бобровицкий район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 2 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.12
    <>,Bobrovitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Bobrovitsa,Bobrovitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nezhin,town,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Kobyzhcha,Bobrovitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Lukashovka,Bobrovitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Novy Bykov,Bobrovitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Novaya Basan,Bobrovitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Bobrovitsa district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Varva district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Варвинский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 2 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.13
    <>,Varva,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Varva,Varva,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Priluki,Плискуновка,suburb,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Antonovka,Varva,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Zhuravka,Varva,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Varva district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
  - Lists of Jews from the Koryukovka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Корюковский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 16 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.14
    <>,Koryukovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Koryukovka,Koryukovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kholmy,Kholmy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kholmy,village,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Kozilovka,Kholmy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Kamka,Kholmy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Syadrino,Koryukovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Aleksandrovka,Koryukovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Savinki,Koryukovka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Koryukovka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 270 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Novgorod Severskiy district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Новгород-Северский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 11 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph Diagram; O.41/1180.15
    <>,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Novgorod Severskiy,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Ostroushki Area ,ravine,Murder Site,Ukraine (USSR); Gorbovo,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Yukhnovo,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Gremyach,Gremyach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Leskonogi,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Vorobyevka,Gremyach,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Pushkari,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Lizunovka,Novgorod Severskiy,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Ushovka,Ponornitsa,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Novgorod Severskiy district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 247 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Repki district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Репкинский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 14 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers Photograph; O.41/1180.16
    <>,Repki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Repki,Repki,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Radul,Lyubech,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Vorobyev,Lyubech,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Dobryanka,Dobryanka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Lyubech,Lyubech,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Nedanchichi,Lyubech,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR); Poddobryanka,Terekhovka,Gomel,Belorussia (USSR); Gornostayevka,Dobryanka,Chernigov,Ukraine (USSR)
    Lists of Jews from the Repki district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers
    The list/s contain approximately 339 names
  - Lists of Jews from the Talalayevka district who perished during the Holocaust or died in battle as Red Army soldiers, Талалаевский район Черниговской области, Украина; 07/2008-09/2008; 2 List of murdered Jews List of Jewish soldiers; O.41/1180.17